>> Kyle Simpson: 在课程概述中，我们讨论了具有以下内容的 JavaScript
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In the course overview
we talked about JavaScript having
三个核心支柱。
three core pillars.
其中一个重要的核心支柱是作用域系统，
And one of those important core
pillars is the scopes system,
JavaScript 如何处理作用域。
how JavaScript deals with scope.
具体来说，正如我们在此演讲中看到的那样，它的名称是词法范围。
Specifically, the name for that, as we'll
see in this lecture, is lexical scope.
那么， JavaScript 的词法范围是什么 ?
So what is the lexical scope
mechanism of JavaScript?
正如你在这里看到的目标是引导我们走向一个模式
And as you see here,
the goal is to lead us towards a pattern
用于改进我们的代码组织的代码。
of code that improves
our code organization.
所以我们需要了解词法范围，以便了解封闭，
So we need to understand lexical scope so
that we can understand closure, and
我们需要了解关闭情况以便了解模块模式。
we need to understand closure so
that we can understand the module pattern.
因此，这就是我们这个讨论单位的目标。
So that is our goal for
this unit of discussion.
我们去潜水吧
Let's dive in.
好的，范围是我们寻找事物的地方。
All right,
scope is where we look for things.
这就是你第一次需要知道的关于这个话题的定义。
That's your first what-you-need-to-know
definition on this topic.
它在哪里寻找
It's where to look for
但这个定义应该会问你几个问题
things, but that definition should ask
a couple of questions in your mind.
第一，我们要找的是什么 ?
Number one,
what is it that we are looking for?
非常简单，我们正在寻找标识。
So very simply,
we're looking for identifiers.
在这里你可以看到一个被分配给
Here you see an x that's
being assigned to, or
一个从一个价值中得到的价值
a y that's being a value retrieved from.
你是否意识到
Whether you realize this or
不是，所有变量都在程序中的两个角色中的一个中。
not, all variables are in one of
those two roles in your program.
所有变量都可以接收某个值的赋值，或者
All variables are either receiving
the assignment of some value, or
您正在从变量中检索值。
you are retrieving a value
from the variable.
这就是，我们的计划中没有其他的变量存在。
That's it, there's no other existence for
variables in our programs than that.
所以我们要做的是从根本上来说
So what we're doing is,
we're fundamentally,
当我们处理代码的时候
when we're processing our code,
when the scope is being
由 JavaScript 引擎处理，本质上是在问问题，
processed by the JavaScript engine,
it's essentially asking the question,
当我看到这个变量的时候，首先是什么位置 ?
when I see this variable,
first of all, what position is it in?
其次，它属于哪个范畴 ?
And secondly,
what scope does it belong to?
换句话说就是
In other words,
这就像是把弹珠配到他们的颜色编码的桶里一样
this is basically like a game of matching
marbles to their color-coded buckets.
如果您认为 JavaScript 引擎处理代码的方式，
If you think about the way a JavaScript
engine processes the code,
它会发现一个变量它会说，嗯，这个是绿色的大理石
it's going to find a variable and it's
gonna say, hmm, this is a green marble so
它就在绿色的水桶里
it goes in the green bucket.
这是一个红色的大理石，所以它进入了红色的桶里。
And this is a red marble, so
it goes into the red bucket.
因此，这基本上是一种把彩色弹珠分类的游戏。
So it's fundamentally a game
of sorting colored marbles.
这是我在谷歌上能找到的最好的照片。
This was the best picture
I could find on Google.
我可以找到颜色的水桶或者找到彩色的弹珠
I could either find colored buckets or
I could find colored marbles,
我找不到他们
I couldn't find them together.
你这有颜色的水桶好吗
So here you go, colored buckets, okay?
好吧但是有一些关于这个定义的细微差别
All right, but there's something
nuanced about that definition that
可能没那么明显，就是这个处理
may not be all that obvious,
which is that this processing that
我们说的是 JavaScript 中的一个实际步骤
we're talking about is an actual
step within JavaScript.
这不仅仅是被处决的原因。
It's not simply inlined
with the execution.
人们认为 JavaScript 是最重要的，这是非常普遍的。
It's extremely common for people to think
about JavaScript as running top down,
按行执行。
line by line, executing.
因为当我们想到解释程序或者动态脚本程序时
Because when we think of interpreted
programs, or dynamic scripted programs,
我们一般认为它们是按直线执行的
we generally think of them as
executing line by line, top down.
所以当我向你断言 JavaScript 不是一种解释语言
And so when I assert to you that
JavaScript is not an interpreted language,
其实其实是一种编译的语言，
but is in fact actually
a compiled language,
可能与你的精神模型不吻合因为你很可能
that may not fit with your whole mental
model because you're probably used to
正在考虑逐行 JavaScript 解释。
thinking of line-by-line
JavaScript interpretation.
让我向你们证明，实际上， JavaScript 是汇编的，或者至少是
So let me prove to you that JavaScript is,
in fact, compiled, or at least,
就像我们会说的一样
as we would say, it's parsed.
有一些处理步骤必须在执行前发生。
That there's some processing step that has
to happen before execution has occurred.
如果您曾经编写过 JavaScript，那么语法错误。
If you have ever written a JavaScript,
syntax error.
从逗号左移，在某处有一个额外的圆括号或卷曲的花括号，并且
Left off a comma, had an extra
parenthesis, or curly brace somewhere, and
然后尝试运行程序，并且立即出现语法错误。
then you try to run the program, and
you immediately got a syntax error.
即，在第 10 行上有语法错误，但您立即
That is, say you have a syntax error
on line 10, but you immediately
在执行第 1 到 9 行之前报告给您的错误。
get that error reported to you before
lines 1 through 9 have executed.
你可能从未停止询问，但问题是问。
You may never have stopped to ask,
but the question bears asking.
如何使 JavaScript 了解第 10 行的语法错误
How is it possible that JavaScript
knew about the syntax error on line 10
在执行第 1 到 9 行之前，除非 JavaScript 实际
before executing lines 1 through 9,
unless JavaScript actually went
首先，通过一个处理步骤，而不是简单地执行顶向下 ?
through a processing step first as
opposed to simply executing top down?
有一些处理步骤，那么处理步骤是什么样的 ?
There was some processing step, so
what does that processing step look like?
我是一个老的编译器理论在我的电脑科学日
Well, I'm an old compiler theory nerd for
my computer science day.
我是那些写编译器来取笑的怪人之一
I am one of those weird folks
that writes compilers for fun,
我喜欢那样做
I enjoy doing that sort of stuff.
在编译器理论中，编译器基本上有四个阶段。
And so in compiler theory, there
are essentially four stages to a compiler.
有时候头两个结合到一个阶段，有时是分开的，
Sometimes the first two are combined into
one stage, sometimes they're separate,
我的课本都是分开的
my textbook had them separate.
所以有了理兴和记号化。
So there's lexing and tokenization.
正在进行分析
There's parsing,
将标记流变成了抽象的语法树。
which turns the stream of tokens into
what's called an abstract syntax tree.
最后一步就是所谓的代码生成，抽象化
And then the last step is what's called
code generation, taking an abstract
语法树，并生成该程序的某种其他可执行形式。
syntax tree and producing some kind of
other executable form of that program.
基本上就是 57 个字，给你一个计算机科学学位，对，
That's basically, in 57 words,
a computer science degree for you, right,
或者至少是编译器理论对吧
or at least compiler theory for
you, right?
这就是我们的程序从文本代码中得到处理的方式
That is how our program gets
processed from its textual code and
可以执行的某种表示形式的源格式。
your source format into some kind of
representation that can be executed.
现在，很多人认为，由于我的原因， JavaScript 无法编译。
Now, a lot of people think, well,
JavaScript can't be compiled because I
不要在我的开发机器上运行编译器
don't run a compiler on my
development machine and
然后将编译后的代码关闭到其他位置。
then ship off the compiled
code to some other location.
所以换句话说，很多人都在思考这个差异。
So in other words, a lot of people
think about this difference between
将其解释和编译为二进制的分发模型。
interpreted and compiled as
the distribution model for the binary.
但这并不是真正的正确的轴线。
But that's not really the right
axis to be thinking about.
右轴是在执行代码之前处理的代码吗 ?
The right axis is, is the code
processed before it is executed or not?
我们确实有语言存在
We do have languages that exist which
通常在执行前不进行处理。
generally don't get
processing before execution.
例如， Bash 脚本。
For example, Bash script.
在 Bash 脚本中，如果在第 4 行上写了格式错误的命令，那么第 1，2 行和第 2 行
In a Bash script, if you write a malformed
command on line 4, lines 1, 2, and
3 号要跑了
3 are gonna run.
当第 4 行失效时可能会把事情搞砸
And when line 4 fails that
might screw stuff up,
因为您要撤销 [LAUGH] 第 1 行，第 2 行和第 3 行。
because you wanna undo [LAUGH] lines 1,
2, and 3.
这是一个永久的问题，类似于真正的脚本语言。
This is a perpetual problem in something
like a true scripting language.
但在 JavaScript中
But in JavaScript,
如果在第 10 行上有语法错误，那么在第 1 到 9 行上不会发生任何情况。
if you have a syntax error on line 10
nothing happens on lines 1 through 9.
必须进行处理，以检查其格式是否正确，格式是否正确，程序。
It has to be processed to check that it's
a well-formed, correctly formed, program.
因此，我们正在执行这些汇编步骤。
So this is going through
these compilation steps.
我提出这个编译器理论的原因是
And the reason I bring up this
compiler theory to talk to you
关于 JavaScript 是编译型语言的原因是我们需要思考
about JavaScript being a compiled language
is because we need to think about
当所有这些大理石桶分类发生时
when all this marble
bucket sorting happens.
如果你想想这个大理石桶在运行时发生的事情
If you think about this marble bucket
sorting stuff is happening at runtime,
原来不仅是一个不准确的心理模型，
it turns out that not only is that
an inaccurate mental model, but
它可以在程序中创建错误，因为
it turns out it can create bugs
within your program because
你认为某些事情是真实的而某些东西是不一样的
you assume something to be true and
something is different.
这种分岐，还记得法律吗 ?
That divergence, remember the law?
这一分化让你觉得
This is a divergence where
you think something and
电脑会想到其他的东西
the computer thinks something else.
猜猜谁赢了
And guess who wins?
电脑好吗
The computer, okay?
所以我们想做的是把我们的大脑像电脑一样
So what we wanna do is try to align
our brains more like the computer,
我们想像编译器一样思考
we want to think like a compiler.
好消息是尽管我们要谈的是编译器
The good news is that even though we're
gonna talk a little bit about compiler
理论上还有一堆我们要彻底掩饰的
theory, there's a whole bunch of it
that we're gonna completely gloss over.
这一讨论的复杂性不重要。
Bunch of complexity that is not
important for this discussion.
但最重要的是我们的大理石分类。
But the one thing that is
important is our marble sorting.
大理石分类是最关键的
Marble sorting is the thing.
本质上是通过比喻来处理我们的范围
It is essentially that metaphorically is
processing of our scopes and putting all
这些标识，就是彩色弹珠，变成了它们正确的存储区。
of these identifiers, that is the colored
marbles, into their correct buckets.
所以在我们执行之前先处理的方式
So the way that processing first
happens before we execute,
有一个阶段它贯穿了所有这些汇编
is that there is a stage where it
goes through all of that compilation,
它经历了所有这些解析，并生成了这个抽象的语法树。
It goes through all of that parsing, and
it produces this abstract syntax tree.
但它也产生了一个词法环境的计划。
But it also produces, essentially,
a plan for the lexical environment.
那就是，所有的词法范围都是，有什么 marbles 会在它们当中，
That is, where all the lexical scopes are,
and what marbles are gonna be in them,
什么标识。
what identifiers.
它准备此计划，即可执行代码
It prepares this plan, and
that is the executable code that is
由 JavaScript 引擎的另一部分执行，好吗 ?
handed off to be executed by the other
part of the JavaScript engine, okay?
现在有人会说，比如说， Java，那是一个编译的
Now, some people would say, for
example, Java, well, that's a compiled
语言，因为我编译它然后分发字节码。
language because I compile it and
then they distribute a bytecode.
事实证明， JavaScript 几乎是一样的。
It turns out,
JavaScript does almost the same thing.
有一个解析器通过您的 JavaScript 源代码进行解析，并生成，
There is a parser that parses through your
JavaScript source code, and it produces,
本质上，中间表示与字节码不相似。
in essence, an intermediate representation
not that dissimilar from a bytecode.
然后把它交给 JavaScript 虚拟机
And it hands it off to
the JavaScript virtual machine,
它嵌入在同一个 JavaScript 引擎中。
which is embedded inside of
the same JavaScript engine.
它解释所有这些事物，它解释的事物之一是，
And it interprets all that stuff, and
one of the things that it interprets is,
每当它进入一个范围它就会创造出所有的弹珠
whenever it enters a scope
it creates all the marbles
根据该计划的要求
according to what
the program told it to do.
所以不管你喜欢编译器理论，我们都得思考
So whether you like compiler theory or
not, we have to think about
JavaScript 作为双通道系统，而不是单通道。
JavaScript as a two-pass system
rather than a single-pass.
如果你只把它当作单道来结束
If you think it only as a single-pass,
you end up having to do all
以避免对您的程序进行不正确的分析。
sorts of other contortions to avoid
incorrect analysis of your program.
我还看到一些虫子在思考范围界定
And I have seen a number of bugs where
people have thought about scoping
不正确。
incorrectly.
所以我们想让我们把这个弄明白
So we wanna make sure we dig in and
get this.
当我们处理代码时发生了什么我称之为编译
What happens when we process our code,
which I would call compilation,
如果你觉得它更好的话就不重要了
if you feel better calling it parsing,
doesn't matter.
但我们要先处理代码然后设置作用域
But we are gonna process the code first,
and set up the scopes, and
那我们就要开始执行了好吗
then we are gonna execute it, okay?
我想知道，或者我想谈谈那些桶是从哪里来的。
And I wanna understand, or I wanna talk
about, where those buckets come from.
那么，如果这些标识是弹珠，那么存储区是什么 ?
So if the identifiers are the marbles,
what are the buckets?
这些桶是我们的范围
Well, the buckets are our units of scope.
在 JavaScript 中，我们主要有功能，但我们现在也有了块。
And in JavaScript we primarily have
functions, but we also now have blocks.
就像几年前的 ES6 一样，我们有一些街区。
As of ES6, a few years ago,
we have blocks.
因此，您具有功能，并且有块，这些是作用域的单位。
So you have functions and you have blocks,
those are the units of scope.
这就是 JavaScript 的组织方式。
That's how JavaScript organizes them.
那是我们的水桶
Those are our buckets, and
当我们在处理代码的过程中遇到这些范围时，我们就会创建它们。
we create those whenever we encounter
those scopes as we process the code.
然后我们就有了弹珠
And then, we have the marbles.
每次我们看到一个大理石在我们的节目中被引用
We create those every time we see
a marble being referenced in our program,
我们为它创造一个大理石然后把它放到适当的桶里
we create a marble for it and
drop it in the appropriate bucket.